(Previously)
Why didn't you wake me up last night?
You literally passed out.
How could I wake you up?
You're definitely sulking.
I was exhausted last night.
I really was.
Why is trying to do something
for the person you love
so exhausting?
Is a rescuer like me not good enough?
If you have to try this hard for love,
does it really make sense?
I think I'm going to ask for some space.
Don't be paranoid yet.
You just started dating.
Exactly.
Maybe it'll hurt less to end it sooner
rather than later.
I'm not letting you leave me!
I'll fight!
I'll fight for us!
I said I'd fight.
I've decided to step into this battlefield.
I'm a dog barking at a plane.
I'm a fighter.
Kanit!
Are you okay?
Toto.
Ow!
Why are you hugging me?
I thought you died
and rotted away in your room.
You didn't pick up the phone.
You didn't answer when I knocked.
I won't die.
I'm just sick.
Whoa, you're burning up.
Have you seen a doctor yet?
I wanted to, but I didn't
have the energy to drive.
Why didn't you call me? I can take you.
You're going to catch
my cold after that hug.
I won't. I'm strong.
I have a great immune system.
But I'm worried about you.
"A Dog and A Plane"
(Episode 9)
ONLY THE DETERMINED WILL WIN
You have a lot of tattoos.
Didn't it hurt getting them?
It's just like love.
It hurts,
but it's beautiful.
What?
I just want to keep looking at your face.
Are you playing a lovestruck guy?
I love you.
- I love you.
- Enough.
Enough. Why do you keep saying that?
Because I want to.
Hey.
Promise me one thing.
From now on, you have
to tell me everything, okay?
No sulking or overthinking
things on your own.
Is there anything
you want to tell me right now?
Hmm…
I forbid you from going to work tomorrow.
Hmm?
I'm taking you on a date.
A date?
To make up for how little
we've seen each other lately.
I know you're exhausted from work.
I want you to relax.
I'm going to go hard.
I like hard.
♪ Huy lay hui, ha ha ♪
♪ Huy lay hui, hey hey ♪
♪ Hey, let's try it, hey ♪
♪ Let's fight it ♪
Arms to the side.
♪ Don't get worn out now, hey, let's push it ♪
Hey.
You might as well
not even look at the instructor.
You're just making up your own moves.
I can't focus anymore.
How can you even keep up?
This is even more exhausting
than rescue work.
I thought you said
this was going to be a romantic date.
That's exactly why I
brought you to work out.
You have to take better
care of your health.
Where would I find the time?
I have to work.
Then I have to eat.
Then I have to find time to sleep.
And then I have to wake up for work again.
It's a neverending loop.
If you keep this up,
you're going to cut your life short.
What? Why are you jinxing me?
I'm not.
But you have to work out
so you can live a long life
and be with me for a long time, got it?
So that's why you brought me to work out?
Yeah.
Come on.
You're more romantic than I thought.
Why are you hugging me?
There are lots of people here.
We're supposed to squat.
Go!
Okay.
I can keep dancing for another hour.
So I can be with you for a long time.
I can do this for another hour.
Bring it on, coach.
So I can…
So I can be with you for a long time.
- Come on.
- Come on, everyone.
So I can be with you for a long time.
Jump!
Let's go!
Hey.
Turn this way.
Hmm?
This will make you look handsome.
What?
Am I not handsome right now?
You're already handsome,
but you'll get even more handsome.
Any more handsome than this
and I'm basically Win Metawin.
The audacity.
If I get more handsome
and people start flirting
and checking me out,
won't you be jealous?
I want to be jealous sometimes.
Can I?
Ugh.
Classic soap opera interruption.
Who is it?
It's Pailin.
I'll wait outside.
What's up?
(What's up, bestie?)
(What are you doing?)
You called right on time.
I brought Toto to the gym.
(Oh.)
(What a sporty couple.)
(Any love scenes happening?)
(You totally forgot about me.)
If you're calling to
scold me, I'm hanging up.
(Wait.)
(I was just teasing you a bit.)
(I just wanted to ask if you've heard back
from Magic Sky Airway.)
Yeah.
But I haven't told Toto.
(What? Why haven't you told him?)
I'll just tell him if I
actually get the job.
(Come on. It might become a problem.)
I know.
I have to go.
Come on!
Dribble faster.
Dribble properly. Next one.
Faster. What even is that jump?
Goalie, keep moving.
Let's see some footwork.
Come on, last one!
Let's take a break here.
Hello, new P.E. teacher.
Oh. What brings you here?
I took a bus.
Okay.
Throwing my own joke back at me, huh?
I got you some snacks.
Thank you.
I'm surprised you know
I love pandan pancakes.
I've been paying attention for years.
Now that I see you in the P.E. uniform,
I can't help but worry.
Worry about what?
I worry about the kids
who'll have a crush on you.
You know what?
A P.E. teacher like you
is the main reason kids turn gay.
So, how's your first day of teaching?
I haven't really gotten the hang of it yet.
Being a teacher isn't easy at all.
You need patience.
Playing and teaching
are different skill sets.
You can take your time.
But what I know for sure is
your talent can definitely help the kids.
Will you come watch me every day?
Sorry, but I have a job to do.
I'm not free like when I was in grade 10.
I need emotional support.
How about you quit being a flight attendant
and become an English teacher here?
So we can be the school's
hot teacher couple.
No.
Being a cheerleader is what I do best.
What are you doing?
The kids saw that.
I couldn't stop myself.
Come on. You're a teacher.
You need to be a good role model
for the kids.
I am being a good role model.
How am I not?
Coach, should we practice?
You two can save the romance for later.
We're jealous here.
Hurry up, Coach.
Stop flirting.
See? I told you.
You guys are in for a rough time.
Go.
Go now.
Come on.
Come on, To!
You know what? If I weren't a rescuer,
View Kunlavut wouldn't even stand a chance.
I'd smash the net to shreds.
Whoa.
You know why?
Don't tell me…
It's because…
Everything Toto.
Everything what?
Come on.
Serve it up.
Hey.
Ouch!
Namo Toto.
Fall hard for Toto.
Heal this bump.
Poof!
All better.
Better now?
Enough.
There, that's one.
You don't have to baby me like this.
I have to take care of you,
not the other way around.
Really?
What are you wearing?
Wow, you got your name embroidered too?
I called and asked your junior
to prepare it for me.
But you make it look so expensive.
Look at me.
So, how are you going to
take care of me today?
Here.
I brought some healthy stuff for you.
Salad.
Vitamins.
Sunscreen.
Fish.
Fruits.
Grapes.
These are so healthy.
Guava.
And here's a salad dressing.
If you keep doing this for me
and I get used to it, what will you do?
I'm demanding, you know?
I don't only want your heart.
I want your body too.
You're always so wild, aren't you?
Now that I got this for you,
you have to apply it before coming to work.
Apply it on both your face and body.
No.
I want you to apply it for me.
It'll absorb better.
Come on.
Do I have to apply to be a rescuer?
I think I qualify.
I have the skills. You already taught me.
No need. It's exhausting.
Your job is exhausting enough.
Being a rescuer takes true passion.
You can't just do it
because you want to please me.
You're better off working in the sky.
Seeing your effort today is enough for me.
It's not enough.
I can do a lot more for you.
Turn around.
Let me give you a massage.
Lean back.
Lie down.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Here.
- I'm lying down then.
Want some balm?
Can you give me a B to B?
Let's save that for our room.
Then can we go to our room now?
You pervert.
Don't people in a relationship get tired?
They have to be everything for each other.
That's too exhausting.
I'd better stay single without skills.
It hurts!
I'm not even pressing hard.
Just gently.
(Rescue unit needed.)
This will sting a bit.
Good thing the wound on the outside
isn't anything serious.
But you still need a doctor to check it out.
Also, please get a certified helmet.
Don't buy cheap stuff.
Please invest in your life.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
Stop lecturing him. He's in pain.
Let's take him to the hospital.
Help me lift him.
Wow, you're giving me orders now?
Yes, darling.
Oh, you two are dating?
A rescuer couple.
Working together.
Love among bloodstains.
Still got a smart mouth, huh?
Get on by yourself, then.
I can't.
Let's go.
Come on.
- One. Two. Three.
What are you doing?
I don't even know what tired is anymore.
Go.
The injured person is waiting.
Tomorrow is your day off.
Do you want to stay over tonight?
So we can spend time together.
Sure.
Do you want to go out tomorrow?
Let's go.
We can go to the temple
to pray for blessings
or ask for an auspicious wedding date.
Wedding?
Wow. Do you have the dowry?
Yes.
Oh.
Toto.
Why didn't you tell me
you saw Mom recently?
I didn't think it was important,
so I didn't tell you.
Lew, can you put the laundry in the machine
and start it for me?
I've already washed everything.
Not yet.
There's my laundry too.
Hello.
- Hi.
- I'm Kanit. Toto's boyfriend.
Oh, really?
You're good-looking.
You look good together.
Thank you.
Toto hasn't told me anything.
Ignore her.
She won't be back after this.
Tonlew said
you've been working hard lately.
I've been working hard my whole life.
One needs to work for money.
I don't want to mooch off anyone.
Tonlew also said you're starting a company.
Can I help?
There's no need.
I've been taking care
of myself my whole life.
I'll find the money.
I know you're angry with me,
but can't you give me a chance?
People make mistakes in life.
So you're trying to make it up
by throwing money at me?
Go ahead.
Yell at me all you want.
But can you please accept this?
Whose money is that?
Your husband's again?
If you don't care about yourself,
at least think about your sister.
I guess this is all I can do.
You're just doing this
to make yourself feel better.
You don't care about Lew and me.
Still thinking about your mom?
I don't want to accept her money.
I don't want to owe her anything anymore.
I understand you.
You have every right
to be angry with your mom.
And I won't say anything
to change your mind.
But about your company,
I have some money.
Do you want to use it for now?
No.
I don't want to trouble you.
You have your own expenses.
Not anymore. I already bought the condo.
Besides, I've been wanting
to invest my money anyway.
I think your start-up has
the potential to go far.
What do you mean?
If you don't want to borrow my money,
how about you let me
invest in your company?
I'll be investing in
something I believe in.
And I believe you can become a frontrunner.
Just go for it.
It'll be our success.
Are you sure it's a good idea?
They say running a business
with your partner is a breakup risk.
Let them talk. I don't care.
I only care about how you feel.
No one has ever believed in me this much
in my entire life.
Hey, Beer.
You're handsome, bro.
As always.
Why? Where are you going?
I'm going to pick up my boyfriend
from the airport.
Pick up your boyfriend from the airport?
Do you have a roll-on?
Can I borrow it?
You should start carrying your own.
Go buy one.
And you should buy a new one.
Look, it's literally bubbling.
Oh, by the way,
someone sent you a letter this morning.
What letter?
Looks like one of those donation envelopes.
Really?
Can you put my money in?
Sure.
Want a smack?
Why so aggressive?
Who knows what letter it is?
Look at you all dressed up though.
I think this one is good.
It's decent enough to work in
and not very expensive.
Try it.
What do you think? Good?
Why? You want me to review this chair?
Mm.
Well…
Now I'm hooked after trying it.
I can sit for a long time
without feeling sore.
It stays hard.
Pure bliss.
You're starting to get as wild as me.
Oh, it's always been in me.
You just woke it up.
Try sitting in it for real.
Good?
Hey.
Won't this break easily?
Really?
Yeah.
Why don't we invest in one that lasts?
That way, it'll be worth it.
A long-term investment.
Here. Look.
Here.
This one is an ergonomic chair.
It's good.
When you sit for long hours in the office,
it'll save your back.
You can almost buy a motorbike
with this price.
It's so damn expensive.
Come on.
It's a good long-term investment.
Choosing a chair is
like choosing a partner.
You have to choose the one
that's good and expensive
so it'll be worth it.
Let me try it then.
Hey, no.
You're heavy.
I'll get this one.
It's expensive
but soft, comfortable,
and good for the heart.
It won't break easily.
It'll stay with me for life.
Can you afford it?
I'll pay in installments.
Ahh!
I'm wheeling this to the register.
Here.
Look at this place.
The size is perfect for a starting office.
Do we really need this much?
Of course, we do.
You're building a start-up.
It has to be this much.
But I'll be working alone.
Look, you might be working alone now,
but later you'll register your company
and you'll need staff
for the kind of work you do.
When clients start flooding in,
you'll need the space.
Look here.
Right when you open the door,
I'll set up a counter
to welcome the clients.
This will be an area for the staff
to take care of them.
And that room over there
will be the meeting room
so you can plan ahead.
I understand,
but I think this is a
little too big for my start.
Hey, you have me as your partner.
I know.
But I want my first office
to feel a bit more like me.
Like a shophouse.
Hmm, that actually makes sense.
We might reach more locals that way.
Yeah, and we can always
think about expanding later.
We can even have a 10-storey building
when the time comes.
You'll be the president
and CEO of Everything Toto.
And what's your role?
I'm yours, CEO.
I can be anything you want me to be.
We'll be each other's future.
Hey, if I weren't a flight attendant,
we'd have more cozy
time like this together.
Soon, when we work together,
we'll always be sweet like this.
We could go at it any way,
anywhere,
and anytime we want.
I guess we won't get to work.
Oh, we can work while we eat.
Here.
Mango?
Go ahead and eat it.
I want you to eat it.
This mango is good.
I want more mangos.
It's all gone.
Can you get more as a topping?
Let me go get some more.
When you're Toto's boyfriend,
you get to eat everything you want.
You want to eat mango?
I'll bring a whole garden to you.
Oh!
HEY, I MADE IT INTO MAGIC SKY AIRWAY.
Damn.
Coming right up.
Mango for Toto's boyfriend.
Thank you.
Come on.
It's a whole mango.
Let me feed you.
Wow.
How is it?
Mm.
It's good.
Eat more.
Eat it with this.
SUVARNABHUMI AIRPORT
Hey, Ki.
Why did you come pick me up
at the airport today?
I wanted to see you.
I wanted to talk to you.
What's wrong?
Why do you look like
you just got chewed out?
LETTER FROM MILITARY
This is…
I have to report for the military draft.
If I'm unlucky,
I'll be stuck in the army for two years.
You won't get drafted.
People will volunteer.
I don't know.
But if I do get drafted, I'll have to
completely overhaul my life plans.
Don't overthink it.
You won't be that unlucky.
Even if you get drafted,
we can still figure it out together.
Right?
Damn it!
Why now?
Right when I got a boyfriend.
Oh, Ki.
If love has no obstacles,
it wouldn't be romantic.
Right?
Don't worry.
CLOSED TODAY FOR A PRIVATE EVENT
Where are you taking me, Lew?
We're almost there.
Hold onto me tight.
Don't worry.
Sit down and I'll take off your blindfold.
Where do I sit?
Careful.
Okay. Can you take it off now?
Alright.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Is it my birthday?
Damn.
I've been working so
hard I lost track of time.
Thank you so much, guys.
And not just your birthday,
we're celebrating your new company too!
We've booked your favorite artist.
Who?
Give it up for.
LOSO!
What?
Really?
Are you serious?
♪ If life is a struggle ♪
♪ One must be able to keep going ♪
♪ Know what's in your heart ♪
♪ Make sure you get there at last ♪
♪ Because life is a fight ♪
♪ Learn with all your might ♪
♪ No matter how far the journey is ♪
♪ Only dreamers could make it ♪
♪ I'm one of the people ♪
♪ Fighting this battle ♪
♪ With the great power of faith ♪
♪ Equal start ♪
♪ And same baseline ♪
♪ Ready your heart ♪
♪ Keep it steadfast ♪
♪ Just dare to dream high ♪
♪ And make it come alive ♪
♪ Be confident ♪
♪ You're on the right track ♪
♪ Block the noise outside ♪
♪ Pay it no mind, keep the fire within ♪
♪ Only the determined will win ♪
Hey, is it over already?
Hold up!
Can we sing the hook again?
Please, sing the hook one more time.
Come on.
♪ Just dare to dream high
and make it come alive ♪
♪ Be confident, you're on the right track ♪
Magic Sky Airway will be proud.
When my friend moves to Dubai,
I'll definitely miss him.
Who's going to Dubai?
Oh? Kanit, of course.
He got his new wings for Dubai.
Come on.
You forgot your own birthday.
I had to ask Tonlew.
What do you think of my surprise?
You like it?
I put so much effort into this, you know?
I had to recruit Je Zo and Beer's help.
Am I cool enough to join your gang now?
Oh.
What's wrong?
Are you stunned? You're so quiet.
Why didn't you tell me?
Tell you what?
That you got a job with a new airline
and have to move abroad.
Well, I've been meaning to tell you,
but I couldn't find the right time.
I didn't want you to overthink.
Of course, I'd overthink.
But I'm so happy for you.
You made your dream come true.
Even if we have to do long-distance.
Come on.
I'm not moving there for good.
It's just for a while, then I'll be back.
But we have so little time for each other
as it is.
If we love each other enough,
no matter how far apart we are,
we can make it work.
Next time,
please tell me things right away.
Don't let me find out from someone else.
I promise.
I'm so proud of you.
Can I ask for one thing?
What is it?
Can you sing for me again?
Again?
♪ Block the noise outside ♪
♪ Pay it no mind, keep the fire within ♪
♪ Only the determined will win ♪
In just a few months,
you'll be wearing a different uniform.
I think I'll miss you in this one.
But it's okay.
I like you in every outfit.
Me too.
Whether you wear white, blue,
or this red fertilizer giveaway shirt,
I like it all.
I don't think it's the outfits.
You just like the person.
Hey.
Hmm?
I haven't gotten you a gift yet.
You don't have to.
Come on.
Having you as my boyfriend
is the most precious gift in my life.
Oh, you're always so dramatic.
But I'll buy you a gift anyway.
How about I take you to join
the Mile High Club?
What's that?
Well, that means…
We're going to do it on the plane.
I'm in.
I like it.
That's exciting.
How about this flight?
- Let's go.
- Stop. Are you crazy?
I'm just kidding.
I'm glad we're growing on our own paths.
And I appreciate your support.
Let's succeed together.
I'm going then.
Hey!
Did you forget something?
You forgot that.
See you when you're back.
Mm.
Here.
This is Phra Boonrod.
Super sacred.
Put it in your mouth before you draw.
You'll survive. Trust me.
Hey!
You're supposed to blow on the head.
- That's spit!
- Come on.
It's sacred.
Bro.
You're definitely getting drafted.
What the hell?
There are so many volunteers.
You'll be safe.
Black!
I'm safe, Mom!
Number 107.
Red! Red!
Black!
Yay!
Red!
Army, Batch 1!
- Black!
- Red!
Black! Black!
Red!
Army, Batch 1!
Are you scared?
Based on statistics,
red shows up less than three times.
The next one is going to be black.
I'd even bet my house on it.
Trust me. It'll be black.
It's black for sure.
Number 121.
You got this, Ki!
Black! Red!
Red! Black!
Black! Black!
Black!
Red!
It has to be red!
Black!
Come on.
It's definitely red!
Black!
Red!
Army, Batch 1!
It's red, bro!
Why the hell are you cheering?
Red means he got drafted.
Oh, shit.
Go.
We just got together, and now
we have to be apart from each other.
I'm sorry.
I should've done military reserve training
in school
instead of focusing on football,
which got me nowhere in the end.
Don't blame yourself.
No one could've known.
I'm so upset.
I just became a teacher.
I'm just three months away
from getting tenured.
I don't even know what I'll be like
when I get out of the military.
It's okay.
When you get out,
we'll figure it out together.
Life isn't as hopeless as it seems.
Hey, where are you going after we land?
I have a boyfriend.
Of course, I'm going to see him.
Yeah, you and your bragging.
I think I'm going shopping.
You're going shopping?
Mm-hmm.
Look at the weather. It's raining
hard. You'll get struck by lightning.
Oh, I'm used to this weather.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are currently experiencing
some turbulence.
Please remain seated
and fasten your seatbelts immediately.
Hey, it's shaking too much.
Excuse me.
We're experiencing some turbulence.
It's normal.
Please don't worry.
Please fasten your
seatbelts for your safety.
Excuse me, please fasten your seatbelt.
Hey!
I don't think this is normal.
Sir, please have a seat.
Please fasten your seatbelts.
Please stay calm.
Don't panic.
Am I falling?
THANK YOU FOR
BEING MY LIFE ADVENTURE.
GO ACHIEVE YOUR DREAMS.
NO MATTER WHERE YOU ARE,
I'LL ALWAYS BE ROOTING FOR YOU.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You scared me. I thought you were a shark.
If I were a shark,
“Sharks love to nibble on you.”
Were you about to say that line?
I see right through you.
You're onto all my cheesy lines.
Are you running around in my heart?
Oh.
Come on.
You still found a way to flirt with me.
Tell you what.
You don't have to flirt anymore
because you already have my body
and heart.
But I still want more.
I'll keep flirting with you and throwing
cheesy lines at you until you're old.
Come on.
It's always like this in the beginning.
Even salty seawater
can become sweet.
Listen.
Even if it's the beginning,
the middle, or the end,
I'll still love you like this.
If a shark comes,
I'll fight it with my bare hands.
I'll beat it until it drowns.
Or if a Tsunami comes,
I'll surf us out of danger.
I'll be here, on standby for you 24/7.
Hey.
Who are you? Aquaman?
I'm Toto.
Toto is your everything.
Are we falling?
No!
Why is it shaking harder?
This isn't normal.
Hey, To.
To.
Let's go.
We need some beer to take the edge off.
We can't.
Why not?
The foundation just called.
What's the latest update?
The plane made an emergency landing
and slid off the runway.
There are injuries and deaths.
People died?
How many?
They reported just one,
but I'm still not sure.
I'm sure he's fine.
I'm not just worried about my partner.
Our job is to worry about everyone.
Ki, Ja-O, let's split
up to help the injured.
Sure.
How are you feeling?
Hey, To!
This person is bleeding so much.
Take him to the hospital now.
Hey!
Sorry.
Tong, have you seen Kanit?
Not at all.
The rescue team is here.
You're fine now. You're safe.
Toto!
This way, Toto!
Oh.
Hey!
Please check on Kanit.
- His leg is badly hurt.
- Are you okay?
I'm okay. Help him first.
Please come with me.
Excuse me!
Could you please take the injured?
This way.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Does your leg hurt?
Let me see.
Be gentle.
I think I hurt it while rushing
to help the passengers.
I thought I lost you.
I thought the same.
When I was on the plane,
your face flashed through my mind.
At the time, I thought,
if I was going to die,
at least I got to kiss you goodbye.
Stop saying things like that.
Do you have any idea how worried sick
I was while driving here?
Just the thought of losing you
is more than I can bear.
Easy.
It's okay. I'm here.
It's okay.
(Next Episode)
I'm going to be based abroad.
Are you okay with that?
I'm happy for you.
But I'm worried about you.
You just got into an accident.
I don't want you to go through anything
like that again.
I'll be away for two years.
If you find someone better than me,
you deserve it.
Telling me to find someone else
is so insulting.
Hey!
Sir.
I have a project to pitch.
I'm going to propose to Kanit.
With me, he'll never shed a tear.
But I still don't like it.
The important thing I want to hear about
isn't money.
What I want to know is
why it has to be my son Kanit.